(Penny(in hallway):)Okay, you guys, look, I know this is none
of my business, but I just... I have to ask.
(Penny(in hallway):)What's Sheldon's deal?
- What do you mean, "deal"?
- You know, like, what's his deal?
(Penny:)Is it girls? Guys? Sock puppets?
(Leonard:)Honestly, we've been operating
under the assumption that he has no deal.
- Oh, come on, everybody has a deal.
- Not Sheldon.
(Howard:)Over the years, we've formulated many
theories about how he might reproduce.
I'm an advocate of mitosis.
(Penny:)I'm sorry?
(Howard:)I believe, one day, Sheldon will eat
an enormous amount of Thai food...
(Howard:)...and split into two Sheldons.
(Leonard:)On the other hand, I think Sheldon
might be the larval form of his species.
(Leonard:)He'll spin a cocoon
and emerge two months later...
(Leonard:)...with moth wings and an exoskeleton.
(Penny:)Okay, well, thanks for the nightmares.